[{"answer": " They're fantastic", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Your sister is an unbelievable cook", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " It's, uh, you never kno", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "He's not a loser at all", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " He's such a loser", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Oh, he's such a loser", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend, yes", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Child molestation is a touchy subject..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Read the papers!  Half the country's doing it", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " We ne", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Everything's good.  Everything's fine", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " Here, you guys.  Open them up", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Really?  That'll be terrific for him, I think", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I think he'll find that satisfying", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I think so", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Really?  That'll be terrific for him, I think", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I like him.  I think he's a sweet guy", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " That's really nice", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " You know, he's been wanting a mitt", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "We need more bread and some baked las", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Uh, no, the shrimp puffs are my friend's.  I do the, uh, crpes caviar", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh.  Well, I liv", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Yes, I do", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " You seem tense.  Is everything all right?  You feel okay", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " No", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " No", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Yes", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " ", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Yes, I'd...", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Page a hundred and twelve", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Bye", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Could you have ruined yourself somehow", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " I don't know.  Excessive masturbation", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " my friend's done this whole new series that I'm sure you would really love", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yeah.  Some of them...yeah, some of them are very big", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " It's not that big a deal.  We just didn't hit it off", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Are you okay?  You loo", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Oh, don't say those words", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " Why, you know the situation", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Oh, no, no.  Well, yes!  I love you", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Oh, no, no, no.  It, uh, i", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " No", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " Tch, well, you know, eventually it, it is going to happen to all of us", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Oh, you know what.  I'm suffocating", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yes, we're going to have this conversation again.  I...I have to leave.  I have to move out", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I don't know.  I thought, maybe I'd move in with my parents for a while", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " Well, maybe it'll only be temporary, but I h", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Tch, oh.  I always told you you would leave me.  But...does it have to be now", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " Oh...my friend, you are my whole world.  Good God!  Have you been kissed tonight?", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": " Who is it", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "But who?  Where did you meet him", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": " I can't hear you.  I can't hear anything.  I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm gonna lose hearing in my ear!  I'", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": " I, I, my ears are experiencing a meltdown!  I can't hear anything", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": " I didn't say that", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " My God!  Wh", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": " Ohh", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": " I know, n", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": " But I'm seeing him", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": " Gee, um...  I...I don't know what to say", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " Who thinks about such nonsense? Now I'm alive.  When I'm dead, I'll be dead", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " Of what?  I'll be unconscious", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": " Oh, that's putting it mildly.  We did everything but exchange gunshots", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Good.  How are you", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Yeah, it was", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": " Oh...well, yo", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": " You've always hated my taste in the past", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "You have", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": " Hmm.  I think it's lucky I ran into you.  Maybe", "docId": "hannah.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": " Oh, well", "qsentId": 72}]